David Soren popular sheet music collection, 1839-1974
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
David Soren popular sheet music collection, 1839-1974
MS 365
Soren, David
1.25 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
The David Soren Collection of Popular Sheet Music, documents an approximately 150 year period in the creation, production, and dissemination of American popular music. These musical scores mirror trends in both American popular music and American history and culture. Full of pathos and emotion, these scores evoke feelings of patriotism, nostalgia, and gaiety. Apart from their musical value, many of these scores are beautifully decorated and like the music, the cover art represents significant trends in American art and fashion.
Organization
This collection is arranged alphabetically by score
Scope and Content Note
Well known titles in the Collection include, "Alexander's Ragtime Band," "Cheek to Cheek," "The Entertainer," "Over There," "Riders in the Sky," "Smoke Gets In Your Eyes," "Stars and Stripes Forever," and "You Were Meant For Me." Well known composers include, Irving Berlin, George Gershwin and Ira Gershwin, Al Jolson, Paganini, Cole Porter, Rogers and Hammerstein, and John Philip Sousa. Musical genres include American patriotic, song and dance, romance, Dixie, and ragtime.
Access Terms
Berlin, Irving N.,; 1888-
Gershwin, George,; 1898-1937
Gershwin, Ira,; 1896-
Jolson, Al,; d. 1950
Paganini, Nicolò; 1782-1840
Porter, Cole,; 1891-1964
Rodgers, Richard,; 1902-
Hammerstein, Oscar,; 1895-1960
Sousa, John Philip,; 1854-1932
Popular music -- United States
Popular culture in art -- United States
Composers -- United States
Ragtime music -- Scores
Patriotic music -- United States -- Scores
Dixieland music -- Scores
Romanticism in music -- Scores
Dance music -- United States -- Scores
Container List
- Sheet Music
  - Across the Border, 1917 Tallmadge, Kirby A Composer (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admiral Dewey March, 1898 Van Riper, Alva Composer (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admiral Dewey's Grand Triumphal March, 1898 Marcel, P. Composer (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adorable, 1933 Whiting, Richard A Composer Marion, George Jr Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - After the War is Over Will There Be Any 'Home Sweet Home', 1917 Woodruff, Joseph Composer Pourmon, E.J. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander's Ragtime Band, 1938 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - All I Do is Dream of You, 1934 Brown, Nacio Herb Composer Freed, Arthur Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - All That I Ask of You is Love, 1910 Ingraham, Herbert Composer Selden, Edgar Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alla En El Rancho Grande, 1934 Uranga, Emilio D. Composer Costello, Bartley Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - America Here’s My Boy, 1917 Lange, Arthur Composer Sterling, Andrew B. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - America’s Victory Sweet Liberty, 1918 Ford, Frank W. Composer Johnson, Bessie V. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Amor, 1941 Ruiz, Gabriel Composer Skylar, Sunny Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary Song, 1946 Jolson, Al and Chaplin, Saul Composer Jolson, Al and Chaplin, Saul Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Song Revue, 1917 Onivas D. (Arranger) Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anvil Chorus, The, undated Krausse, Theo Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arrah Wanna: An Irish Indian Matrimonial Venture, 1906 Morse, Theodore Composer Drislane, Jack Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Au Revoir, But Not Good-bye (Soldier Boy) (Two Copies), 1917 Von Tilzer, Albert Composer Brown, Lew Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Back to the Carolina You Love, 1914 Schwartz, Jean Composer Clarke, Grant Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Battle of New Orleans, The, 1959 Driftwood, Jimmy Composer Driftwood, Jimmy Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Battle of Spion Kop March, The, 1900 Butler, M.W. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Battle of Waterloo, The, undated Anderson G. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beautiful Ohio Song, 1918 Earl, Mary Composer Macdonald, Ballard Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Beside a Garden Wall, 1926 Short, Albert E. and Delbridge, Del Composer Kahn, Gus Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Big Brown Bear, The, 1919 Mana-Zucca Composer Mana-Zucca Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Black Key Polka Mazourka, undated Winner, Sep. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Blue and the Gray, The, 1884 Sudds, W.F. Composer Finch, F.M. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Blue-eyed Sally, 1924 Bernard, Al. and Robinson, Russel Composer Bernard, Al. and Robinson, Russel Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Break The News To Mother (Two Copies), 1897 Harris, Chas K. Composer Harris, Chas K. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bridal Bells Waltz, 1897 West, L.E. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bring Back My Soldier Boy to Me, 1918 Magine, Frank Composer Hirsch, Walter Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Brown Eyes Has That Little Maiden, 1875 Osgood, Geo. L. Composer Laurius Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - California and You, 1914 Puck, Harry Composer Leslie, Edgar Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Camp Custer, 1917 Schroeder, Ed. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Carrie or Carrie Marry Harry, 1909 Von Tilzer, Albert Composer McCree, Junie Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Celebrated Witches Dance, The, 1880 Paganini Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chapel Chimes, 1913 Greenwald, M. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cheek to Cheek, 1935 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Cinderella, 1906 Powell, W.C. Composer O’Dea, Jas. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut March, The, 1911 Nassann, William Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Convent Bells or Les Cloches Du Couvent, 1877 Bollman, Henri Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Corsican Girl, The, 1889 Holst, Eduard Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cow-Cow-Boogie, 1941 Raye, Don and De Paul, Gene Composer Raye, Don and De Paul, Gene Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cutey, Tell Me, Who Tied Your Tie?, 1910 Edwards, Ed. Composer Longbrake, Arthur Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Daisy Song, A, undated Gatty, A.Scott Composer Gatty, S.H. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dance of the Honey Bells, 1906 Wurtele, G.F. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dance With a Dolly (With a Hole in Her Stockin'), 1954 Shand, Terry, Eaton, Jimmy and Leader, Mickey Composer Shand, Terry, Eaton, Jimmy and Leader, Mickey Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dancing In The Dark, undated Schwartz, Arthur Composer unidentified Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dancing Tambourine, 1927 Polla, W.C. Composer Ponce, Phil Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dark Eyes, 1929 Fassio A. (Arranger) Composer Raven, Carol Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Day By Day, 1945 Cahn, Sammy, Stordahl, Axel, and Weston, Paul Composer Cahn, Sammy, Stordahl, Axel, and Weston, Paul Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dear Mom, 1941 Harris, Maury Coleman Composer Harris, Maury Coleman Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dear Old Pal of Mine, 1918 Rice, Gitz, Lieut. Composer Harris, Maury Coleman Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon Grand March (Cover Only), undated Pease, Alfred H. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dinah, 1913 Marshall, Henry L. Composer Murphy, Stanley Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dixie Volunteers, The, 1917 Leslie, Edgar and Ruby, Harry Composer Leslie, Edgar and Ruby, Harry Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dixie Volunteers, The, 1917 Leslie, Edgar and Ruby, Harry Composer Leslie, Edgar and Ruby, Harry Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dizzy Fingers, 1923 Confrey, Zez Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dolly Varden (Selection from,), 1801 Edwards, Julian Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Don’t Try to Steal the Sweetheart of a Soldier, 1917 Van and Schenck Composer Bryan, Alfred Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Don’t You Wish You Were Back Home Again, 1913 Harris, Chas. K. Composer Harris, Chas. K. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Down On The Farm, 1839 Williams, Jas. T. Composer Williams, Jas. T. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Down South Everybody’s Happy, 1917 Paley, Herman Composer Vincent, Nat Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Down Where the Daisies Grow, 1917 Eastman, A.H. and Heltman, Fred Composer Eastman, A.H. and Heltman, Fred Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dreaming Love of You, 1907 Harris, Chas.K. Composer Harris, Chas.K. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dutch Lullaby, A, 1889 Jordan, Jules Composer Field, Eugene Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - El Fresco Galop, 1880 Garland, A.C. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Empty Saddles, 1936 Hill, Billy Composer Hill, Billy Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Entertainer, The, 1973 Joplin, Scott Composer Brimhall, John Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Entertainer, The, 1974 Joplin, Scott Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Every Little Movement, 1910 Hoschna, Karl L. Composer Hauerbach, Otto Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ferry-Boat Serenade, 1939 Di Lazzaro, E. Composer Adamson, Harold Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Fickle Mollie, 1883 Bischoff, J.W. Composer Dowe, Jennie E.T. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Follow the Swallow, 1924 Henderson, Ray Composer Rose, Billy and Dixon, Mort Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Forty Second Street, 1932 Warren, Harry Composer Dubin, Al Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Four Little Blackberries Schottische, 1907 O’Connor, Lawrence B. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Freedom Train, The, 1947 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - From Here to Shanghai, 1917 Berlin, Irving Composer Berlin, Irving Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gaby Glide, The, 1911 Hirsch, Louis A. Composer Pilcer, Harry Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Give Your Smiles to All the Boys But Keep Your Heart For Me, 1910 Mohr, Halsey K. Composer Mohr, Halsey K. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Glory of Love, The, 1936 Hill, Billy Composer Hill, Billy Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Glory of Spring, The, 1928 Rubens, Maury Composer Brennan, J. Keirn Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Good Company (Cover Missing), undated Adams, Stephen Composer unidentfied Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Good Company (Cover Missing), undated Adams, Stephen Composer unidentified Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Good Morning Mr. Zip-Zip-Zip!, 1918 Lloyd, Robert, Army Song Leader Composer Lloyd, Robert, Army Song Leader Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Goodnight Mother, 1940 David, Mack; Bryan, Al and Lawnhurst, Vee Composer David, Mack; Bryan, Al and Lawnhurst, Vee Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Gotta Be This or That, 1945 Skylar, Sunny Composer Skylar, Sunny Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Grandmother’s Love Letters, Memories of Long Ago, 1905 Bishop, Chas. Composer Gordon, Janet Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Greyhound March, The, 1912 Parker, John Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hail to the Stars and Stripes, 1919 Miller, Joseph Composer Miller, Joseph Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Hail! Hail! The Gang’s All Here (What the –Duece – Do We Care), 1917 Morse, Theodore and Sullivan Composer Esrom, D.A. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Have You A Little Fairy in Your Home?, 1911 Daniels, Chas. N. (Moret, Neil) Composer Hawkins, G.H.E., Gillespie, Arthur Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Have You Ever Been Lonely? (Have You Ever Been Blue?), 1933 De Rose, Petper Composer Brown, George Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Heavenward, 1875 Tours, Berthold Composer REA Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hero Girl’s Dream, The, 1909 Labitzky, Aug. Composer Labitzky, Aug. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hi-Ho, 1936 Gershwin, George Composer Gershwin, Ira Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hooks and Eyes, 1914 Harris, Chas. K. Composer Harris, Chas. K. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - How ‘Ya Gonna Keep ‘Em Down On The Farm (After They’ve Seen Paree?), 1919 Donaldson, Walter Composer Young, Joe, Lewis, Sam M. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Huckleberry Finn, 1917 Hess, Cliff, Lewis, Sam M., Young, Joe Composer Hess, Cliff, Lewis, Sam M., Young, Joe Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - I Can’t Stop Loving Your Now, 1914 Snyder, Ted Composer Kalmar, Bert, Leslie, Edgar Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - I Got to Go Where Your Are’ Chlo-e (Song of the Swamp), 1927 Moret, Neil Composer Kahn, Gus Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I Hate to Lose You I'm So Used to You Now, 1918 Gottler, Archie Composer Clark, Grant Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I love you so much it hurts, 1948 Tillman, Floyd Composer Tillman, Floyd Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I May Be Gone for a Long, Long Time, 1917 Von, Tilzer, Al Composer Brown, Lew Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I Never Knew How Much I Loved My Soldier Boy Until He Marched Away, 1918 Rundell, Leon P. Composer Rundell, Leon P. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I Want to be a Lidy, 1901 Talbot, Howard Composer Dange, George Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I Want You Just You, 1915 Paley, Herman Composer Klein, Lou Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I Wonder How the Old Folks Are At Home, 1909 Vandersloot, F.W. Composer Lambert, Herbert S. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I’ll Change the Shadows to Sunshine, 1913 Ball, Ernest R. Composer Graff, Geo. Jr. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I’ll Come Back to You When It’s All Over, 1917 Mills, Kerry Composer Brown, Lew Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I’m Crying Just for You, 1913 Monaco, James V. Composer McCarthy, Joe Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - I’m Glad I Can Make You Cry, 1918 McCarron, Chas. R., Morgan, Carey Composer McCarron, Chas. R., Morgan, Carey Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - I’m Sorry I Made You Cry (Three Copies), 1918 Clesi, N.J. Composer Clesi, N.J. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - I’m Waiting My Darling For Thee!, undated Evans, Geo. T. Composer Evans, Geo. T. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - If He Can Fight Like He Can Love Good Night, Germany!, 1918 Meyer, Geo. W. Composer Clarke, Grant, Rogers, Howard E. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - If I’m Not at the Roll Call Kiss Mother Good-bye For Me, 1918 Boyden, George L. Composer Boyden, George L. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - In A Little Spanish Town (Twas On a Night Like This), 1926 Wayne, Mabel Composer Lewis, Young Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - In Dreamy Panama, 1914 Bennett, Theron D. Composer Norton, Geo A. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - In God We Trust, The American National Anthem, undated Chapple, W.W. Composer Chapple, W.W. Lyricist (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - In Maytime Reverie, 1916 Reeg, Geo. A. Jr. Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In the Evening By the Moonlight, 1880 Bland, Jas. A. Composer Bland, Jas. A. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In the Garden of My Heart, 1908 Ball, Ernest R. Composer Roma, Caro Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In The Orchard Where The Children Used to Play (Two Copies), 1901 Walker, Barclay Composer Riley, James Whitcomb Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In the Shadow of the Dear Old Blarney Stone, 1913 Barron, Ted S. Composer Havez, Jean C. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In the Shadows, 1911 Finck, Herman Composer Goetz, E. Ray Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - In The Still of the Night, 1937 Porter, Cole Composer Porter, Cole Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Indian Love Call, 1924 Friml, Rudolf Composer Harbach, Otto, Hammerstein, Oscar Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - It Can’t Be Wrong, 1952 Steiner, Max Composer Gannon, Kim Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - It Does’nt Matter Though Your Hair is Gray, 1913 Klickmann, F. Henri Composer Callahan, J. Will Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - It’s A Long, Long Way to Tipperary, 1912 Judge, Jack, Williams, Harry Composer Judge, Jack, Williams, Harry Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - It’s Always Nice Weather Indoors (From the Sunday Sentinel), 1908 Henry, S.R. Composer Lamb, Arthur J. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - It’s Not Your Nationality (It’s Simply You), 1916 Johnson, Howard Composer McCarthy, Hoe Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - I’ve Got You Under My Skin, 1936 Porter, Cole Composer Porter, Cole Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ja-Da, 1918 Carleton, Bob Composer Carleton, Bob Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jerry (You Warra a Warrior In the War) (First Page Only), 1919 Baskette, Billy Composer O’Neil, Dannie Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jerry (You Warra a Warrior In the War) (First Page Only), 1919 Baskette, Billy Composer O’Neil, Dannie Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Jingle Bell Galop, 1895 Butler, M.W. Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Just a Night for Meditation, 1928 Pollack, Lew, Young, Lewis Composer Pollack, Lew, Young, Lewis Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Just Like Washington Crossed the Delaware, General Pershing Will Cross the Rhine, 1918 Meyer, Geo. W. Composer Johnson, Howard Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - King and I, The (Vocal Selections), 1951 Rogers, Richard Composer Hammerstein, Oscar Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kinky-Head, 1924 Morris, Edward Composer Gardiner, Maud Luise Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kiss That Made Me Cry, The, 1918 Gottler, Archie Composer Burns, Joe, Fields, Arthur Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kiss That Made Me Cry, The, 1918 Gottler, Archie Composer Burns, Joe, Fields, Arthur Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Kitty, 1901 Solomon, Frederic Composer Goodwin, J. Cheever Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - La Fiesta Tango, 1914 Moret, Neil Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Laddie, A True Blue Song, 1914 Moore, Luella Lockwood Composer Lawton, J. Fred Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lamb that Strayed from the Fold, The, undated Carleton, Sidney Composer Davis, Harry Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Last Night Was the End of the World, 1912 Von Tilzer, Harry Composer Sterling, Andrew B. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lay Down Your Arms, 1915 James, Charles Composer Small, Louise Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Le Reveil Du Lion (Cover Missing), undated Cover Missing Composer Cover Missing Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Let Me See You Smile, 1905 Fischer, Fred Composer Fischer, Fred Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Let’s All Be Americans Now, 1917 Berlin, Irving, Leslie, Edgar, Meyer, Geo. Composer Berlin, Irving, Leslie, Edgar, Meyer, Geo. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Let’s Bring New Glory to Old Glory, 1942 Warren, Harry Composer Gordon, Mack Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Liberty Bell (It’s Time to Ring Again) (Two Copies), 1917 Mohr, Halsey K. Composer Goodwin, Joe Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Light Cavalry, 1924 Von Suppe, Franz Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lily of the Valley, 1905 Smith, Sydney Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lingering, 1911 Spear, Henry C. Composer Spear, Henry C. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Listen to the Knocking at the Knitting Club, 1917 Von Tilzer, Harry Composer Hanlon, Bert Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Little Angel, The: A Sequel to Little Barefoot, undated Merrill, H.T. Composer Furman, Josephine Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Little Beauties, 1881 Haven, Claude Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Little Bit of Sunshine (From Home), A, 1918 Hanley, James Composer MacDonald, Ballard, Goodwin, Joe Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Little By Little, 1929 O’Keefe, Walter, Dolan Bobby Composer O’Keefe, Walter, Dolan Bobby Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Little Grey Mother Who Waits All Alone, The, 1915 De Costa, Harry Composer Grossman, Bernard Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Little Maid Milking Her Cow, The, undated Molloy, J.L. Composer Molloy, J.L. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lonesome Road, The From Show Boat, 1928 Shilkret, Nathaniel Composer Austin, Gene Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Love Will Forgive and Forget, 1910 Furth, Seymour Composer Heelan, Will A. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Love Your Spell is Everywhere, 1929 Goulding, Edmund Composer Janis, Elsie Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Love’s Ship, 1920 Morrison, Alice Nadine Composer Morrison, Nellie Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lucy-Anna-Lou, 1905 Edwards, Gus Composer Madden, Edward Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mam’selle Marie (From Five Imaginary Early Louisiana Songs of Slavery ), 1929 Guton, David W. Composer Lussi, Marie Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mary Dear (Some Day We Will Meet Again), 1922 De Costa, Harry, Jerome, M.K. Composer De Costa, Harry, Jerome, M.K. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Melody of Love, 1903 Engelmann, H. Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memories of France, 1928 Robinson, J. Russel Composer Dubin, Al Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mem’ries (Golden Memory Days), 1928 Sanford, Harold Composer Neely, Henry M. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mendelssohn’s Wedding March, undated Von Mendelssohn, Felix Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mickey, 1918 Moret, Neil Composer Williams, Harry Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Military Waltz, 1917 Logan, Frederic Knight Composer Logan, Frederic Knight Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Min Kones Mand (From Kongerevuen), 1916 Christine Composer Christine Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mister Gallagher and Mister Shean, 1922 Gallagher, Ed Composer Shean, Al Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Missouri Waltz (Hush-A-Bye, Ma Baby), 1914 Logna, Frederic Knight (Arranger) Composer Shannon, J.R. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Molly Lee, 1909 Morse, Theodore Composer Mahoney, Jack Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Moonlight On the Colorado, 1930 King, Robert A. Composer Moll, Billy Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - More I See You, The, 1945 Warren, Harry Composer Gordon, Mack Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mother’s Welcome At the Door, 1884 Estabrooke, H.M. Composer St. Clair, Geo. F. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Mountain Stream, The, undated Smith, Sidney Composer no lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - My Baby's Arms, 1919 Tierney, Harry Composer McCarthy, Joseph Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - My Carolina Rose, 1921 Hall, Wendell W. Composer Hall, Wendell W. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - My Country I Hear You Calling Me, 1916 Dreyer, Dave Composer Grossman, Bernie Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - My Heart is with the U.S.A., 1915 Burn, Farrar Composer Burn, Farrar Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - My Isle of Golden Dreams, 1919 Blaufuss, Walter Composer Kahn, Gus Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Napoleon’s Last Charge (Two Copies), 1910 Paull, E.T. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - National Echoes March, 1906 Ellis, J. Henry Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - National Emblem March, 1907 Bagley, E.E. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New Russian Rag, The, 1923 Cobb, George L. Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - New York’s Jubilee March, 1923 Nicosia, Richard Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - O’Brien Has No Place to Go, 1908 Evans, George Composer Murphy, Stanley Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Oh! What a Pal Was Mary, 1919 Wendling, Pete Composer Leslie, Edgar, Kalmar, Bert Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Oh! Your Million Dollar Doll, 1913 Abrahams, Maurice Composer Clarke, Grant, Leslie, Edgar Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Oh Johnny, Oh Johnny, 1917 Olman, Abe Composer Rose, Ed. Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Old Spinning Wheel, The (Two Copies), 1933 Hill, Billy Composer Hill, Billy Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - On Account-a I Love You, 1934 Stept, Sam H. Composer Green, But Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - On the Boardwalk (in Atlantic City), 1946 Myrow, Josef Composer Gordon, Mack Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - On the Road to Mexico Through Dixieland, 1914 Van Alstyne, Egbert Composer Callahan, J. Will Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - One Heart, One Soul, undated Strauss, Johann Composer No Lyrics Lyricist (Box 2, Folder 9)